Bui Minh Hieu



Front-End Engineer in Vietnam -Walter Cipher &-

Detail-oriented Front-End Engineer with a strong focus on building intuitive, high-quality web applications, and a passion for creating smooth and efficient user experiences using the latest technologies.

- https://hieu-buiminh.io.vn
- https://hieu-buiminh-resume.vercel.app
- https://github.com/Hieu-BuiMinh
- minhhieu2122000@gmail.com
- +84 838 739 523



ABOUT

I am a 25-year-old Front-End Engineer from Vietnam, born in 2000, and you can also call me Walter Cipher. I specialize in the React ecosystem and have experience working with TypeScript, Next.js, React.js, Node.js, and database management. Currently, I am passionate about learning UI/ UX design.

In addition to my work as a Front-End Engineer, I also run a blog at hieu-buiminh.vercell.app, where I share insights on web development, technology, and personal experiences. Through my blog, I aim to inspire and educate others in the tech community, as well as document my journey of continuous learning and growth.

I love using Next.js to create a website. Then use GitHub to host my codebase. After that, I use Vercel to deploy it. Here are my current favorite tech stack

























SKILLS Present

- 3+ years experience in web developmen
- · Have deep knowledge about HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Typescript, UI Frameworks as AntDesign, Mantine, Shadon UI Single Page Application
- · Understand the concept and philosophy of ReactJS NextJS component and lifecycle.
- · Have solid knowledge about React Hooks, Redux, and other state management library as Zustand.
- Experience in working with Turborepo and NextJS 14-15
- · Work well with source control such as Github, GitLab, Jira





Node js



















Design Systems

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

2018 - 2022

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City

Front-end programmer vocational Vietnam Australia Vocational College

2020 - 2022

Bui Minh Hieu



Front-End Engineer in Vietnam

-Walter Cipher &-

Detail-oriented Front-End Engineer with a strong focus on building intuitive, high-quality web applications, and a passion for creating smooth and efficient user experiences using the latest technologies.

- https://hieu-buiminh.io.vn
- https://hieu-buiminh-resume.vercel.app
- https://github.com/Hieu-BuiMinh
- @ minhhieu2122000@gmail.com
- # +84 838 739 523



WORK EXPERIENCE

BIM-Next App 2024 - Present

Company: IDECO Vietnam

Building Information Modeling (BIM) enables users to view 3D models, generate reports, and manage working time on construction sites. By integrating real-time data, it offers a comprehensive overview of the project, making it easier to track progress, optimize resources, and ensure timely delivery. The platform also helps manage work schedules and monitor time effectively, boosting overall site productivity.

Pluxee Vietnam 2022 - 2023

Company: Softworld VietNam

Distributing web app systems, buying vouchers and promotional codes, posting news information, buying phone cards, scanning QR codes, promoting the brand, and becoming a partner with the parent company. Focus on customers, consumers, and employee benefits

Pluxee admin site 2022 - 2023

Company: Softworld VietNam

Voucher distribution management system to manage articles, customer lists, user accounts, brands, promotions and notifications to users

Thiso-mall admin site 2022 - 2023

Company: Softworld VietNam

Thiso Mall Salas system allows admins to manage articles, brand management, promotions, user information, mall map management, receipt scanning history, and event schedule to enhance the Experience amenities that help you visit and shop more safely, conveniently, and completely.

<u>TConnect</u> 2021 - 2022

Company: TMA Solutions

As a project to manage projects, manage many projects in the system in the form of a dash board Statistics of projects being managed by each account equipment management Monthly statistics of alarms... The alt screen notifies the device error

- There are 3 types of accounts: Manager (all role)
- · Supervisor: manage a project, only one supervisor
- · Technician: no permission to add update

<u>RMS-Container</u> 2021 - 2022

Company: TMA Solutions

RMS - Reefer Monitoring System is a system to help manage reefer containers remotely with the main features:

- Customer management
- Equipment Management (Containers)
- · View container status in real time
- Get aler
- · Download PTI Log

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

2018 - 2022

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City

Front-end programmer vocational

2020 - 2022